[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "What's your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Well, the only real surprise is that it happened tonight, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What impact will Steve Jobs standing down as the chief executive officer have on the company, do you think, if any?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, Steve Jobs is one of the great innovators in the history of modern capitalism.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What's the difference for a company like Apple between the CEO and the chairman, if you're someone as hands-on as Steve Jobs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, that is the whole key of Steve Jobs.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RBR", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "You know, what kind of importance will they put to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Less than you'd think, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "CD", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "What's he always said to you about the condition he's been in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, first of all, Steve Jobs and I do not have what one would call a friendly relationship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "I mean, for someone like Steve Jobs who is so personally linked to this company, who helped build it from nothing, to give up the reins as he's doing, would you imagine that his health has deteriorated pretty significantly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I hate to speculate like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Aren't we all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "He's a genius and he's done an incredible job for his company, also for the American economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Will he have to learn that kind of ability, do you think, to go to these conferences once a year and excite the world the way Steve Jobs does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, I don't think you can learn how to be Steve Jobs.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Would you say that Steve Jobs could lay claim to being the greatest businessman America's ever produced?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I think that's possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "What is the latest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Yes, Piers, the wind has really been picking up over the last couple of hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "What intelligence do we have right now on the direction of Irene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Waiting for that right-hand turn that we always forecast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "So, how unusual is it that the East Coast would be threatened with a hurricane of this magnitude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "We get one about every three years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["East Coast"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chad"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "What should they really be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Well, you know, as Chad mentioned, when there's a hurricane drought, I think people become complacent and ignore what people say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What is your reaction to what you're seeing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Hello, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Now that he's gone, can you see a situation where you would return, perhaps be part of the government going forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "L-SENUSSI: Look, Piers, we have not been outside the country, we've been working from day one in opposition against Colonel Gadhafi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What was your personal human reaction to those scenes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, my reaction is, the tyrant, he's gone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I think -- and maybe we have a false sense of security -- but mostly what's going through your mind is trying to pay attention to what's going on around you, so you can actually report the story in a calm enough manner, so that the person on the other end doesn't feel like it's so out of control, and that you're out of control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Obviously it appears the rebels are pretty much completely in control now, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "They're pretty much in control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Do you, as a dispassionate journalist, share the optimism about what will happen next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Look, you cannot help but be stirred when you're in a situation where there is so much excitement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bahamas"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "And where are you fearing it may be heading?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "UGATE: Right now, still in the Bahamas, some strengthening is the Hurricane Center forecast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "And the storm is getting stronger, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Yeah, it was a category one last night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "So if you're in the area that may be affected here, what is the best advice right now for people who may get hit by this hurricane?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Find out, if you live along the coast, are you in an evacuation zone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "I mean, what is your expert view of what's going on with the weather?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Senator Gregg, let me ask you, first of all, for your reaction to what's happening in Libya?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Obviously it's positive to have Libya finally have the potential of a free government.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gregg"], "LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I think we have to be in any Arab country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "But certainly in terms of positioning Libya going forward to a way that suits America's interests, should America now be getting more involved than it has been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "MD", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Absolutely, there's no question about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya", "America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What's your take on it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, we're facing up to a period of chaos that is brought on by ourselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Wouldn't it be in America's interest to have somebody like you rather than turning down the job of the Commerce secretary, to have accepted it, and to have this fight with the president on the inside of the tent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "That's very kind of you to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Commerce"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Perry"]}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What is your assessment of where the party is now, and moving closer to choosing a nominee?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "REGG: I think Governor Perry is a very strong and viable candidate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Will you be doing that again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I haven't decided.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]